Guide to the Trumbull College, Yale University, Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Trumbull College, Yale University, photographs
1929-1962
RU 609
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
3
The collection contains photographs and slides documenting the construction of Trumbull College at Yale, including interior and exterior views.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 46-B (YRG 46-B), Records and materials documenting individual Yale buildings, facilities, and grounds.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged in four series: I. Construction Progress Photographs, 1930-1933. II. General Views, 1930-1969. III. Oversize. IV. Slides and transparencies.
Scope and Contents
The collection contains photographs and slides documenting the construction of Trumbull College at Yale, including interior and exterior views.
College buildings -- Design and construction; Photographs; Slides (photographs); Trumbull College (Yale University); Yale University -- Pictorial works; Yale University -- Buildings; Yale University -- Student housing
- Construction progress photographs, 1930-1960; Series I
  - Sterling Dormitories
    - 1930 Jan-Feb (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1930 Mar-Apr (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1930 May-June (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Trumbull College
    - 1932 Jun-Jul, excavation (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1932 Aug-Sep (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1932 Oct-Nov (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1932 Dec-1933 Jan (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1933 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 1933 Apr-May (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1933 Jun (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1933 Jul 5, completed exterior (Box 1, Folder 11)
- General views, circa 1920-1962; Series II
  - Site demolition (Sterling Dormitories), 1929 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - General construction views, 1930-1934 (Box 2, Folder 2 - 3)
  - Exterior, 1930-1932, 1941, 1954-1959, undated (Box 2, Folder 4 - 6)
  - Gateway, 1933, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Courtyard, 1930s, 1961-1962, undated (Box 2, Folder 8 - 10)
  - Western court, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Interior, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Interior: dining hall, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Interior: library, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Architect's drawings, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Inscription above western gate on Elm Street (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Oversize, Series III
  - View (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Slides and transparencies, Series IV
  - Slides [glass]
  - Transparencies (Box 4)